<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 William Moreno <williamjmorenor@gmail.com> -->
<!--
     EmailAddress: wolfgang@rohdewald.de
SentUpstream: 2014-09-24
-->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.ksudoku.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ksudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KSudoku</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSudokuxx</name>
  <summary>Complete a numeric puzzle with the numbers from one to nine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Completeu un puzle numèric puzzle amb nombres des de l'u al nou.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Completeu un puzle numèric puzzle amb nombres des de l'u al nou.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Vyplňte číselné puzzle čísly od jedné do devíti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Vervollständigen Sie ein Zahlenrätsel mit Zahlen von eins bis neun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Complete a numeric puzzle with the numbers from one to nine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Completar un rompecabezas numérico con los números del uno al nueve</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Arvmõistatus arvude paigutamiseks ühest üheksani</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Täydennä lukupalapeli numeroin yhdestä yhdeksään</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Complete un quebracabezas numérico cos números do 1 ao 9.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Completa un rompicapo numerico con le cifra da uno a nove</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Maak een numerieke puzzel met de cijfers vanaf één tot en met negen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Fullfør eit slags talpuslespel med siffera 1 til 9</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Uzupełnij układankę numeryczną cyframi od jeden do dziwięciu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Completar um 'puzzle' numérico com os números de um a nove</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Complete um puzzle numérico com os números de um a nove</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Úplné číselné puzzle s číslami od jedna do deväť</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Rešite številčno uganko s številkami med 1 in 9</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Саставите бројевну слагалицу са бројевима од један до девет</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Sastavite brojevnu slagalicu sa brojevima od jedan do devet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Саставите бројевну слагалицу са бројевима од један до девет</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Sastavite brojevnu slagalicu sa brojevima od jedan do devet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Fyll i ett sifferpussel med siffrorna från ett till nio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Розв’яжіть числову головоломку із числами від одного до дев’яти</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxComplete a numeric puzzle with the numbers from one to ninexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KSudoku is a free version of the popular logic game Sudoku developed by the KDE community.
      The game is to fill a nine by nine grid with the numbers from one to nine filling
      the rows, columns and three by three squares without repeating a value on them.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KSudoku és una versió lliure del popular joc de lògica Sudoku desenvolupat per la comunitat KDE. El joc consisteix en omplir una quadrícula de nou per nou amb els nombres des de l'u al nou a les files, columnes i els quadrats de tres per tres sense repetir cap valor en ells.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KSudoku és una versió lliure del popular joc de lògica Sudoku desenvolupat per la comunitat KDE. El joc consisteix en omplir una quadrícula de nou per nou amb els nombres des de l'u al nou a les files, columnes i els quadrats de tres per tres sense repetir cap valor en ells.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KSudoku ist eine freie Version des populären Logikspiels Sudoku entwickelt von der KDE-Gemeinschaft. Ziel des Spiels ist es, ein Gitter mit neun mal neun Feldern mit Zahlen von eins bis neun zu füllen, so dass jede Zahl in den Reihen, Spalten und Quadraten mit drei mal drei Feldern nur einmal vorkommt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KSudoku è una versione libera del popolare gioco di logica Sudoku sviluppato dalla comunità KDE. Il gioco consiste nel riempire una griglia nove per nove con le cifre da uno a nove. facendo in modo che nelle righe, nelle colonne e nei quadrati di dimensione tre per tre non si ripetano gli stessi valori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KSudoku is een vrije versie van het populaire logische spel Sudoku ontwikkeld door de KDE gemeenschap. Het spel gaat over het vullen van een negen bij negen raster met de cijfers vanaf één tot en met negen door het vullen van de rijen, de kolommen en drie bij drie vierkantjes zonder een waarde daarin te herhalen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KSudoku é uma versão livre do conhecido jogo de lógica Sudoku desenvolvido pela comunidade do KDE. No jogo pretende-se preencher uma grelha de nove por nove posições, com os números de um a nove a preencher as linhas, colunas e os quadrados de três por três, sem que se repita qualquer valor nestes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ksudoku är en fri version av det populära logikspelet Sudoku utvecklat av KDE-gemenskapen. Spelet går ut på att fylla i ett nio gånger nio rutmönster, där siffror från ett till nio ska fylla rader, kolumner och tre gånger tre fyrkanter utan att ett värde upprepas i någon av dem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KSudoku — вільна версія популярної логічної гри, судоку, яку розроблено спільнотою KDE. Гра полягає у заповненні таблиці дев’ять на дев’ять клітинок числами від одного до дев’яти так, щоб у кожному блоці таблиці розміром три на три клітинки ці числа не повторювалися.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKSudoku is a free version of the popular logic game Sudoku developed by the KDE community. The game is to fill a nine by nine grid with the numbers from one to nine filling the rows, columns and three by three squares without repeating a value on them.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://games.kde.org/game.php?game=ksudoku</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://games.kde.org/games/ksudoku/screenshots/originals/ksudoku01.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
